Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops,
listening to the evening breeze♪
♪Wine in hand,
I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪The endless night
keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪Years of companionship
vanish like mist♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪The returned soul
wears robes of regret♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪Into a story♪
♪Crushing the past,
I let old memories fade♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=Episode 12=
Kerosene!
Help! I don't want to die!
Help! Help!
Help! Fire! There's a fire!
Protect the City Lord.
Wei Feng, take care
of yourself and the others.
City Lord!
Watch out!
(Tonight I will perish
in this sea of flames.)
(My Four Dreams journey may end here.)
(I never managed to change anything.)
(Wan, may you break free
from the Mu family)
(and live happily from now on.)
My lady.
City Lord...
He's back?
Say it. What happened?
(Spirit Tablet of Deceased Mu Yunqing)
Yunqing, my dear grandson.
Why did you leave us so soon?
How can I face your parents now?
Grandfather, I'll help you back.
Yunqing's spirit in heaven
wouldn't want you to be like this.
Please.
Let me see the City Lord one last time.
Please!
I never thought
our last farewell would be permanent.
You didn't even shave. How unsightly.
♪Wine in hand,
I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
Mu Yunqing, if you're tired
and don't want to get up,
just sleep awhile.
I'm here.
If one day I'm no longer with you,
you must stay happy.
What did you say?
Because I love seeing you smile.
I want you to stay happy.
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪This endless yearning♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
Sparks fall into the sea.
Sun and moon lose their glow.
Farewell, City Lord.
♪Don't let this story end♪
Yunqing died.
Jin City needs a leader.
Our Mu family has few heirs.
Now it's only you.
Yunhao, can you bear
this responsibility?
Grandfather, I won't let you down.
No rush. Think it over carefully.
You failed again tonight.
If it weren't for Mu Yunqing...
Save your excuses.
That day you told us
to assassinate him during his wedding,
but he was prepared,
causing us heavy losses.
You
owe this to us.
Wait!
I have a way to eliminate Yu Yingwan.
You better deliver.
I will.
It's you.
Fine. I'll think it over.
(I'll be the City Lord sooner or later.)
♪Winter snow waltzes
before the courtyard♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪You seem so distant,
yet right before my eyes♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪I dream of standing
with you, side by side♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪To walk with you♪